[{"id":1,"QuestionIndex":"1","Question":"How is your mood, choose a response that is closest to how you’ve been feeling over the previous week?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[\"Always in a good mood\",\"mostly happy the odd bad days\",\"More good days than bad\",\"testing\"]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":2,"QuestionIndex":"2","Question":"How is your mood, choose a response that is closest to how you’ve been feeling over the previous week?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[\"Always in a good mood\",\"mostly happy the odd bad days\",\"More good days than bad\",\"Feel low most of the time\",\"Always feel extremely low\",\"None of these\"]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":3,"QuestionIndex":"1.1","Question":"Can you tell me a bit more about how you’re feeling?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":4,"QuestionIndex":"2.1","Question":"Can you tell me a bit more about how you have been sleeping?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [] }","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":5,"QuestionIndex":"3","Question":"How anxious or on edge do you feel? Choose an answer that’s closest to how you’ve\r\nbeen feeling over the previous week","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [ \"Not anxious at all\", \"Rarely anxious\", \"Sometimes anxious\", \"Anxious more often than not\", \"Anxious most of the time\", \"Always extremely anxious\" ,\"None of these\" ] }\r\n","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":6,"QuestionIndex":"3.1","Question":"Can you tell me a bit more about how anxious you have been feeling","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [] }","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":7,"QuestionIndex":"4","Question":"How stressed do you feel? Choose an answer that’s closest to how you’ve been\r\nfeeling over the previous week","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [ \"Never stressed\" , \"Rarely stressed\", \"Sometimes stressed\", \"stressed more often than not\", \"stressed most of the time\", \"Always extremely stressed\" ,\"None of these\" ] }\r\n","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":8,"QuestionIndex":"4.1","Question":"Can you tell me a bit more about how stressed you’ve been feeling ?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [] }","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":9,"QuestionIndex":"5","Question":"Have you been worrying about anything?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [ \"Coronavirus 19\" , \"Money\", \"Housing\", \"Exams\", \"Personal relationships\", \"Health issue\", \"Smoking, drinking or gambling\", \"Other things\" ] }\r\n","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":10,"QuestionIndex":"5.1","Question":"Can you tell me about more about what is stressing you ?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [] }","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":11,"QuestionIndex":"6","Question":"testing","Answers":"{\"Answers\" : [] }","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":1},{"id":15,"QuestionIndex":"7","Question":"How much chocolate do you eat?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[\"1-2 bars a week\",\"1 bar a week\",\"A few squares a week\",\"none\"]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":0},{"id":16,"QuestionIndex":"8","Question":"how much do you drink?","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[\"1-2  days a week\",\"Occasionally \"]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":0},{"id":25,"QuestionIndex":"9","Question":"testing","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":0},{"id":null,"QuestionIndex":"10","Question":"how are ...","Answers":"{\"Answers\" :[\"\",\"\"]}","Type":null,"Session_Allocation":0}]